<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SynthCatalog</string>
    <string name="dialog_text">This product is selling soon!  Are you sure you want to know about it?</string>
    <string name="menu_information">Information</string>
    <string name="menu_uninstall">Uninstall</string>
    <string name="information_author">Synthkeeper Eugene Clewlow</string>
    <string name="information_telephone_number">TEL: +14085551234</string>
    <string name="synth_title_behrpolyd">Behringer Poly D Polyphonic Analog Synthesizer</string>
    <string name="synth_title_grandmother">Moog Grandmother Semi-Modular Analog Synthesizer and Step Sequencer</string>
    <string name="synth_title_ju06a">Roland JU-06A Boutique Series Juno Sound Module</string>
    <string name="synth_title_minimoog">Moog Subsequent 25 Analog Synthesizer</string>
    <string name="synth_title_system8">Roland System-8 Plug-Out Synthesizer</string>
    <string name="synth_desc_behrpolyd">The first truly portable analog synthesizer was released in 1971. Although it was rather pricey and could be temperamental, keyboard heavies of the era were quick to embrace it; and in the ensuing decades, its celebrated sounds graced countless concerts, records, and film scores. Now Sweetwater is excited to present to you Behringer’s homage to that iconic monosynth, and there are some exciting surprises waiting for all synthesists who have been aching to get their hands on one of these legendary synths. First off, the Behringer Poly D packs four voices of polyphony — instead of one — inside its classic, 37-key wood-trimmed chassis; and second — it is amazingly affordable! Otherwise, it packs all the features of the original — and then some.</string>
    <string name="synth_desc_grandmother">The Moog Grandmother semi-modular analog synthesizer had us at "built-in spring reverb," and there is plenty more creative potential here than meets the eye. You can start playing and designing sounds immediately — no patching required. The onboard arpeggiator and sequencer are a blast to play with, and you can even save three sequences for instant recall anytime. And with its 32-note Fatar keybed, the Grandmother is one of the best-feeling compact analog synths youll find. Whether you need it for stage or studio, the Moog Grandmother offers a fresh take on the classic Moog sound.</string>
    <string name="synth_desc_ju06a">Vintage Juno-60 and Juno-106 synthesizers are sought-after items — their warm sound, rich chorus effect, and hands-on creation capabilities are legendary. Now, courtesy of Roland’s JU-06A module, you can get both synths in one reliable, modern instrument. This module is tailor-made for electronic musicians. Use it with a sequencer via USB or MIDI, play it anywhere thanks to battery operation and a built-in speaker, or even use it as an audio interface for a simple production setup. What’s more, it looks like the real deal by virtue of its classic color scheme and styling. If you’re a vintage synth aficionado, the JU-06A is a must-have item.</string>
    <string name="synth_desc_minimoog">Moog may have put analog synthesis on the map in the 1960s, but the company has never rested on its laurels. The drive to continually advance the state of the art runs deep in Moog’s DNA. Sweetwater is proud to present the Subsequent 25 compact analog synth. The Sub Phatty was a huge hit here, and the Subsequent 25 builds on that legacy, incorporating artist feedback into the evolution of Moog instruments that continue to inspire musicians worldwide. Upgraded with twice the headroom, Moog’s paraphonic Duo Mode, real wood side panels, and much more, the Moog Subsequent 25 sets a new standard in compact analog synthesizers.</string>
    <string name="synth_desc_system8">Generations of keyboard players here at Sweetwater have sworn by Roland synths, and the next-gen System-8 delivers all the sounds weve known and loved for decades. At the core of this awesome synthesizer is Rolands Analog Circuit Behavior engine, fueling three oscillators across eight voices, all loaded with filters, effects, and a massive array of modulation options. In addition to its amazing internal sound engine, Plug-out technology lets you load up completely different synth engines — Jupiter-8 and JUNO-106 Plug-outs included — and you can switch between three models on the fly. Talk about killer sound flexibility! Top it off with an interface thats both classic and futuristic, split and layered synths, an integrated vocoder, and much more. The System-8 offers everything a keyboard player could ask for.</string>

</resources>